sup everyone tan was only five fewer the
very special video today and I know you
[ __ ] know what day it is
that's right everyone it's the second
day of a third month in other words
Sonic Manic and Sonia the Hedgehog's
[ __ ] birthday that is why I haven't
been uploading a video for the past few
days because I've been like getting like
through the whole birthday party setup
and all that [ __ ]
I invited like a [ __ ] ton of people we
all had cake we watch soccer we had of
we ate chili [ __ ] dogs it was
delicious
ah but I knew I couldn't leave you guys
I couldn't leave my [ __ ] [ __ ] with
nothing so I decide we're gonna
celebrate just one one between between
you and me so let's get this [ __ ]
started I already have some cake like I
love like all my friends over like Sonic
Max oh you know cuz you know how it is
they all came over there they [ __ ]
swarm this cake so Bobby took some cake
and shoved it up socks ass I'm not even
[ __ ] kidding it why like sub I mean
before I even put the cake out Bobby
Winlock he went like looking for the
cake he walked her to me and say ain't a
mother a father was the cake I'm gonna
show this on my bitch's ass and I told
him exactly where it was and this a
candle by the way I'm lying this [ __ ] I
mean it was [ __ ] sexy I'm I'm not
gonna lie [ __ ] I'm not [ __ ]
Pinocchio and she I don't I don't tell a
lie
come on what the [ __ ] what the [ __ ]
laughs up you [ __ ] just saying no this
is an actual real candle like my mommy
and daddy they said I couldn't before
have one so I just had to find like a
toothpick or some [ __ ]
it'll get to eventually like we live
during the party there we go [ __ ]
[ __ ]
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday dear balsamic
Underground happy birthday to you come
up how I'm gonna blow out the candle
what the [ __ ] is this this is insane
it's not light enough me I gotta make a
wish okay I can't tell you guys cuz I
won't come true so I got I'm trying some
of this [ __ ] I mean you know I love so
many time I saw his birthday even more
than my own
you know why [ __ ] cuz I love sonogram
you do I want mom die
mm how the [ __ ] done Bobby get inside
but no that's [ __ ] and we are gone
I might stick up my ass